So I come back to where chat, yep.
And this time, I want to use hyper-write to start writing.
But beforehand, I also have this last question of mine.
And I want to ask hyper-write if I can generate any kind
of images or visuals using that.
So I ask it the question.
I click on record audio, and I also have
another question.
And the question is that, can I also generate images
or any kind of visuals using you?
And the other question is that, can I have voice
conversations with you?
So I talk and you talk as well.
Answer these two, please.
And yep.
Let's see what the answer will be.
So I sub it this one as well.
Great follow-up, here's the scoop on those.
For images or visuals, I can't generate or edit images
directly myself, right?
But there's a cool sister.
So this sister thing, we don't have anything to do with it
right now.
It's separated.
But whatever.
Yeah, so what we know so far is that hyper-write.
Yep, the name says hyper-write.
So it just writes, it can generate any kind of images
or visuals or same kind of stuff.
And now about the voice chats, right now,
I'm all about text-based conversations, as you see.
So all we have over here is text-based conversations.